♪ OH, OH, OH, OH, OH ♪ -- 喔喔喔喔喔
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH, OH ♪  -- 喔喔喔喔喔
♪ I MESSED UP TONIGHT ♪ -- 今晚我搞砸了
♪ I LOST ANOTHER FIGHT ♪ -- 又一次的落敗
♪ LOST TO MYSELF BUT I'LL JUST START AGAIN ♪
-- 但我會再度開始
♪ I KEEP FALLING DOWN ♪ -- 我不斷的受挫
♪ I KEEP ON HITTING THE GROUND ♪ -- 不斷的失敗
♪ BUT I ALWAYS GET UP NOW TO SEE WHAT'S NEXT ♪
-- 而我永遠會重新振作 迎接下個挑戰
♪ BIRDS DON'T JUST FLY ♪
-- 鳥並非一直翶翔天際
♪ THEY FALL DOWN AND GET UP ♪
-- 他們也會跌落雲霄而後重新振翅高飛
♪ NOBODY LEARNS ♪
-- 沒有人在學習的過程中
♪ WITHOUT GETTING IT WRONG ♪
-- 永不犯錯
♪ I WON'T GIVE UP, NO, I WON'T GIVE IN ♪
-- 我絕不會放棄 絕不讓步
♪ TILL I REACH THE END ♪
-- 直到我抵達終點
♪ AND THEN I'LL START AGAIN ♪
-- 然後重新出發
♪ NO, I WON'T LEAVE ♪
-- 不，我不會放棄
♪ I WANT TO TRY EVERYTHING ♪
-- 我要嘗試所有事
♪ I WANT TO TRY EVEN THOUGH I COULD FAIL ♪
-- 即使會失敗，我依然想要嘗試
♪ I WON'T GIVE UP ♪
-- 我絕不會放棄 絕不讓步
♪ NO, I WON'T GIVE IN TILL I REACH THE END ♪
-- 直到我抵達終點
♪ THEN I'LL START AGAIN ♪
-- 然後重新出發
♪ NO, I WON'T LEAVE ♪
-- 不，我不會放棄
♪ I WANT TO TRY EVERYTHING ♪
-- 我要嘗試所有事
♪ I WANT TO TRY EVEN THOUGH I COULD FAIL ♪
-- 即使會失敗，我依然想要嘗試
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH, OH ♪ -- 喔喔喔喔喔
♪ TRY EVERYTHING ♪
-- 嘗試所有事情
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH, OH ♪ -- 喔喔喔喔喔
♪ TRY EVERYTHING ♪
-- 嘗試所有事情
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH, OH ♪ -- 喔喔喔喔喔
♪ TRY EVERYTHING ♪
-- 嘗試所有事情
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH, OH ♪ -- 喔喔喔喔喔
♪ LOOK HOW FAR YOU'VE COME ♪
-- 看你一路來走了多遠
♪ YOU FILLED YOUR HEART WITH LOVE ♪
-- 你讓你心中充滿著愛
♪ BABY, YOU'VE DONE ENOUGH ♪
-- 寶貝 你己經做得夠多
♪ TAKE A DEEP BREATH ♪
-- 深呼吸一下
♪ DON'T BEAT YOURSELF UP ♪
-- 不要苛責自己
♪ NO NEED TO RUN SO FAST ♪
-- 不必跑得太快
♪ SOMETIMES WE COME LAST BUT WE DID OUR BEST ♪
-- 只要我們全力以赴夢想就會成真
♪ I WON'T GIVE UP, NO, I WON'T GIVE IN ♪
-- 我絕不會放棄 絕不讓步
♪ TILL I REACH THE END AND THEN I'LL START AGAIN ♪
-- 直到我抵達終點，然後重新出發
♪ NO, I WON'T LEAVE ♪
-- 不，我不會放棄
♪ I WANT TO TRY EVERYTHING ♪
-- 我要嘗試所有事
♪ I WANT TO TRY EVEN THOUGH I COULD FAIL ♪
-- 即使會失敗，我依然想要嘗試
♪ I WON'T GIVE UP ♪
-- 我絕不會放棄 絕不讓步
♪ NO, I WON'T GIVE IN TILL I REACH THE END ♪
-- 我不會放棄，直到我抵達終點
♪ THEN I'LL START AGAIN ♪
-- 然後我會重新出發
♪ NO, I WON'T LEAVE ♪
-- 不，我不會放棄
♪ I WANT TO TRY EVERYTHING ♪
-- 我要嘗試所有事
♪ I WANT TO TRY EVEN THOUGH I COULD FAIL ♪
-- 即使會失敗，我依然想要嘗試
♪ I'LL KEEP ON MAKING THOSE NEW MISTAKES ♪
-- 我也會繼續犯錯
♪ I'LL KEEP ON MAKING THEM EVERY DAY ♪
-- 但我每天都會繼續
♪ THOSE NEW MISTAKES ♪
-- 即使犯錯
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH, OH ♪ -- 喔喔喔喔喔
♪ TRY EVERYTHING ♪ -- 嘗試所有事情
♪ TRY EVERYTHING. ♪ -- 嘗試所有事情